## RITESH KUMAR

# FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER KOREAN LANGUAGE EXPERT



9910645499



rit.kr.7@gmail.com



New Delhi, India







#### SKILLS

- HTML/CSS(SCSS/Tailwind CSS)
- JavaScript / React JS
- SQL
- Translation and Interpretation
- Content Anylist
- Onboarding

#### LANGUAGE

- Korean Advance
- Turkish Beginner

#### HOBBIES

- Trekking/ Camping
- Basketball

### EDUCATION

## HANGUK UNIVERSITY OF FOREIGN STUDIES

#### Seoul, Korea

2018-2019

Exchang Student (Business studies and Korean language)

#### JAWAHARLAL NEHRU UNIVERSITY

#### New Delhi. India

2013-2018

M.A/B.A(Hons) in Korean language literature and cultural studies

#### SAINIK SCHOOL GOPALGANJ

Gopalganj, India

2006-2013

class 6th - Intermediate

## PROFILE

I work well in collaborative environments and enjoy teaming up with others to achieve common goals. I am an effective communicator and can get my message across clearly and concisely. I have a friendly personality and enjoy interacting with others. My ultimate goal is to provide efficient services by combining my expertise.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **AMAZON**

Sr. SD Transalation Associate

July 2021 - Present

- Global Work Authorization(GWA) -Korean language expert
- Daily volume assignment to the team -APAC/EMEA
- Onboarding/Audit/Interview -APAC

#### CONCENTRIX (GOOGLE - YOUTUBE)

Sr. Advisor, Transation - Korean

Oct 2019 - July 2021

- Monetization service Korean language expert
- Youtube Content moderation Analyst

#### UNICORN INCUBATOR(KOREA) - THE GAIN (INDIA)

Market Research Analyst - Intern

June 2019 - Aug 2019

- Help companies to understand their potential cross-border partner
- Translate contract, agreement and other legal documents

### **PROJECT**

#### TIC TAC TOE

This web App is created using ReactJS. The winner is announced at last and we can also trace the histry moves.

#### **SHOPPING CART**

This web App is created using ReactJS where products are displayed and can be categorized according to is available size. Even we can add products to cart and go for checkout.

#### **RESPONSIBE APP**

This web App is created using HTML and CSS where the web design will automatically adjust for different screen sizes and viewports.